and before some people came here to talk
I resolved to expose myself and open this situation
before this all comes out
how can i explain this
I can be the dumbest guy
Choose a relationship
when I went to record the series start with real
in outside judge
and neither I nor he really knew if this was going to work
then I ended up going to Jundiaí
he ended up going after me
we were super excited
ended up getting jealous
beast is on
like the guy was jealous of Juninho from the gas station
I haven't spoken to me for more than twenty days
and then he started to fight
stayed together one day
two days
suddenly he disappeared
was quiet all day
and there I spoke
ge bro doesn't give
and I ended up ending this relationship
a week after we left
I found out that he was already with another guy
living in João Pessoa
it's hard bro
has it overcome
go to Santos to record season three
we ended up talking
and today
I wanted to show you that I'm not alone
I will give this new story another chance